scavengers.ca 2019-08-03

# Privacy Policy – Scavengers Studio

## PRIVACY POLICY

**Effective date: August 16, 2018.**

This Privacy Policy explains how Scavengers Studio (“Scavengers Studio”, “we”, “us”) collects, uses, and discloses information we obtain through [www.scavengers.ca](https://www.scavengers.ca/) (the “Website”) and along with Scavengers Studio’s Game Software and any other applications, products, services, or websites operated by Scavengers Studio that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively with the Website, the “Service”).

Scavengers Studio complies with all applicable laws related to personal information and we strive to protect the rights of individual users by adopting this Privacy Policy in accordance with relevant laws and regulations. Scavengers Studio is the data controller of your personal information.

By using the Service, you consent to the processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**

Personal Information is information that can be used, alone or in combination with other available information, to identify you, such as your real full name, email address, phone number and postal address.

Scavengers Studio generally collects or receives Personal Information in three ways.

1) Provided by you

You may provide us with Personal Information when playing the Game Software or visiting the Website.

  * Email address and name to use customer service.
  * Profile information: When you register for the Service through a platform (e.g. Steam, Microsoft, etc.), we may collect some information you may have provided such as a short bio, individual avatar, or profile photo.
  * Newsletter sign-up: We collect your name and email address if you agree to subscribe to our newsletter. Your name and email address are shared with Mailchimp, our newsletter service provider, for the only purpose to send you our newsletter. You can see Mailchimp’s privacy policy here: <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>

2) Provide indirectly by using the Service

When you use the Service, we may automatically collect the following information:

  * IP address

3) Provided from third party

We offers the Game service through Steam, Xbox, and Twitch platforms, provided respectively by Valve Corporation, Microsoft, and Amazon. We collect the following personal information from these companies to identify individual users.

  * Steam ID, Xbox ID, and Twitch User ID (spectator experience)

**WHAT OTHER INFORMATION IS COLLECTED**

**Information we collect when you use our Service**

We may automatically collect certain technical information from your computer or mobile device when you use the Service.

_Device Information._ We receive information from your device, including web browser type, mobile operating system version (to the extent applicable), and unique device identifiers.

_Usage Information._ We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, we automatically send and receive information to and from your device which we use to automatically update (new features, bug fixes, etc.) our game. We collect aggregate information about the use of our game, including information about users playing the Game Software, such as user-specific behavior, the amount of time played, and the date and time of visits.

_Information from Cookies_. We and our service providers may collect information using cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your computer or other Internet access device. Cookies may enable us to personalize your experience on the Service, maintain a persistent session, passively collect demographic information about your computer, and monitor advertisements and other activities. On the Website, we use Google Analytics to collect and process certain analytics data; Google provides some additional privacy options described at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners).

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use the information we collect about and from you for many purposes, including: providing, supporting, and improving the Service, analyzing how you use the Service, managing our network, and better tailoring content and features. In the majority of cases, processing of your personal information will be justified on the basis that:

– You have consented to the processing of your data

– The processing is necessary to perform a contract with you. For instance, as you go about using our Game Software, we use your information to maintain your account and your profile and to provide Service and customer support to you.

1) Use of Personal Information collected in the Game Software

We may collect Personal Information in order to provide the Service and to improve quality of the Service. This includes:

– Providing customer support by collecting and answering inquiries

– Providing technical support and improving quality of the Service

– Identifying individual users to provide the game service

– Protecting against usage of unauthorized programs

2) Use of non-personal information collected in the Game Software

We may use and collect non-personal information to provide and improve the Service, such as:

– Tracking usage patterns and analyzing user trends

– Protecting against usage of unauthorized programs

– Resolving technical problems and improving server quality

3) Use of Personal Information collected on the Website

We may use your Personal Information to communicate with you:

If you subscribe to our newsletter on our Website, we will use the email address to send you newsletters or other marketing communication.

If you ask for customer support with your email address, we will use the email address to communicate with you.

4) Sharing Personal Information to Third Parties

We may give permission to third parties, including service providers who process personal information on behalf of the company to provide certain services.

Examples of services include:

– customer support services; – cloud storage services; -anti-cheat services;

If we chose to allow third party to process personal information, third party vendors will process personal information only to the extent that is necessary to perform the services requested by Scavengers Studio.

The following companies may process some or all personal information collected by us.

Company: Keywords International Limited

Purpose: Handling of customer support requests

Process: Responding to customer support requests through Zendesk and with the help of proprietary tools. No personal data will be stored on the system of the data processor.

Retention: NA

Company: EasyAntiCheat Oy

Purpose: Detecting and restricting hacking tools and unauthorized programs

Retention: Outsourcing contract is expired or terminated

Sharing of information may involve cross-border data countries outside of the EU and other regions with comprehensive data protection laws. We will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection.

5) Compliance with Applicable Law

We may also process the information we collect about you or from you for the following purposes: (ii) as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency; and (iii) to comply with industry standards and our policies.

6) Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers

We reserve the right to transfer your information to service providers, advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third parties in connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a corporate transaction in which we are acquired by or merged with another company or we sell, liquidate, or transfer all or a portion of our assets.

In addition, we may share anonymous and aggregated reports and information on user demographics and traffic patterns with third parties.

With the exception of the uses specified above, we will not sell, transfer, rent out, share or disclose your personal information to other companies.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION RETENTION AND REMOVAL**

Scavengers Studio utilizes storage facilities run by Amazon Web Services (DynamoDB & S3) and Google Cloud (Google Storage & Google BigQuery) to store your information. Unless a different use/storage period is required by applicable laws and regulation, we will use and store your information for a length of time necessary for the uses explained in this Privacy Policy.

**INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER 13**

The Service is not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect information online from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not submit any personal information to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have gathered any personal information from or about a child under 13 without proper parental consent, please contact us at [support@scavengers.ca](mailto:support@scavengers.ca).

**YOUR RIGHTS**

Subject to limitation in applicable law, you are entitled to object to or request restriction of processing of your personal information, and to request access to, rectification, erasure and portability of your own personal information. To make request, or if you have any other question regarding our privacy practices, please contact [support@scavengers.ca](mailto:support@scavengers.ca) . We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. In certain countries including in the EU, you have a right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how we process your personal information. The data protection authority you can lodge a complaint with notably may be that of your habitual residence, where you work or where we are established.

**HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION COLLECTED**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted video game industry standards to protect personal information submitted to us against loss, misuse, and alteration, both during transmission and in storage. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will inform you of any material data breaches that we discover that may compromise your personal information.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES**

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our information practices or relevant laws. To inform you of any change, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on the Website and indicate at the top of the Privacy Policy when it was updated. If we decide to use particular personal information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will let you know through our Services, by email, or other communication. Your continued use of the services following the changes to these terms will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Policy.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or if you would like to exercise your rights and choices, please contact us at [support@scavengers.ca](mailto:support@scavengers.ca) or by writing to us at Scavengers Studio, 250-1435 St-Alexandre, Montreal (Quebec) H3A 2G4, Canada – attention Legal Department.
